kriscarr.com 2019-07-13

# Privacy Policy - KrisCarr.com

_Updated May 25, 2018_

Thank you for visiting us. Your privacy is important to us, and therefore we have developed this Privacy Policy to make sure that our Sites are positive and constructive spaces where you feel safe.

This Privacy Policy outlines our guidelines concerning the use of your personal information including the efforts we make to protect your personal information and the choices you have concerning our use of such information. Read this Privacy Policy carefully. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice. We will post any changes here so that you will always know our policies regarding what information we gather and how we use and share that information. Refer back to this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference to our Terms of Use.

## SCOPE OF PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy covers only information collected on the Sites in order to provide you with certain Services (such as, but not limited to, all information and opportunities shared with you through our websites and email). It does not cover any information collected offline by us, nor does it cover the conduct of any Third-Party Sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any Third-Party Sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

You may visit our site anonymously. In connection with the Services we may request personal information from you (such as your name, street address, telephone number, credit card number, email address) in connection with your use of, or participation in the Sites or Services. We only collect personal information from you if you voluntarily submit such information to us. We will never intentionally disclose any personal information to any third party without your permission (through opting-in or similar procedures) except as provided for herein or otherwise as permitted or required under Applicable Laws. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information, except as set forth herein.

We collect your information: 

  * To personalize your experience;
  * To improve our Sites;
  * To improve customer service; and
  * To process transactions.

We may contact you based on the information you provide online in connection with the Services or use the information in connection with the performance of the Services. We will share information with necessary third parties for the purpose of carrying out the Services. Your participation in the Services constitutes your consent to such disclosure and use of such information. In the event that your personal information is requested as part of our surveys, polls or promotions, such personal information may be added to your registration information.

If you give us your permission or otherwise “opt-in,, we may use personal information for marketing and promotional purposes. We will give you an opportunity to “opt-in” at the time our request for your personal information is made. Please note, however, that under certain circumstances, if you initially do not choose to “opt-in” or if you later “opt-out,” you may not be eligible for certain benefits or Services for which personal information is required. 

These policies have the following exceptions: We will release specific information to comply with any valid legal inquiry or process or any Applicable Laws. We will also release specific information in special cases, such as if there is an attempted breach of the security of the Sites or a physical or property threat to you or others. We may provide access to your personal information to our contractors who are performing services for us in connection with our Sites or the Services that you have requested. Any information you provide when making a purchase will be shared with payment processors, financial gateways, credit card companies and any other necessary third parties. If you publicly post personal information on our Sites, that information can be collected and used by third parties. Although we strive to protect our users’ privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of information you post on the Sites and have no control over how such third parties may use your information. You disclose such information at your own risk. We strongly suggest that you never post your last name, address or telephone to our Sites. 

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account information and password. You shall be responsible for all uses of your account, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or password. 

If you are within the European Union, see below (Opt-Out and GDPR) to understand the choices you have about the ways we use your personal information.

## NONPERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION

We may collect nonpersonal information through the use of, without limitation, cookies, IP address tracking and web beacons. 

Nonpersonal information might include the browser you use, the type of computer you use, your operating system or your internet service provider. Our systems may also automatically gather information about your location, the areas you visit and search terms you use on our Sites and about the links you may select from within our Sites to other areas of the web or elsewhere online.

We use such information for our business purposes, to administer the Sites, to better manage advertising on the Sites, to understand how our users use our Sites and to improve our Sites. 

We may aggregate and share non-personal information with our partners, suppliers, and other third parties, but we will not share any individual names, personal navigational or other personal information without your consent and we maintain control how your non-personal information will be used. For example, we may use a third-party advertising company to customize ads and share demographic and preference information to display advertisements appropriate for you. We may contract with a third-party web analytics provider to help optimize our Sites. 

More About IP Addresses: An “IP address” is a unique number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you connect to the Internet. It is used to identify your computer’s “location” in cyberspace, so that the information you request can be delivered to you. IP addresses do not include your name, email address, or other information that identifies you personally, but in some cases, they can be used to identify you. For example, if you have registered with this Site, we may link your IP address to account information that identifies you personally. We may also provide your IP address to our third-party service providers who can use it to identify your state and zip code. This gives us valuable demographic information about the individuals who use this Site. In addition, if we suspect inappropriate or criminal activity or a threat to the security of this Site or its users, we may share our server logs—which contain users’ IP addresses—with the appropriate investigative authorities, who could use that information to trace and identify individuals.

## OPT-OUT AND GDPR

We provide opportunities to unsubscribe/opt-out from our Services in all newsletters and marketing emails and you may choose to do so at any time.

If you live in the European Union, you may also use the unsubscribe/opt-out features to request that we redact your personal information from our records. We will comply within a reasonable time and, in any case, within the time limits established by applicable law. We may ask you for additional information to verify your identity. In some cases, however, we may limit or deny your request if the law permits or requires us to do so or if we are unable to verify your identify.

If you need further assistance with unsubscribing or opting-out of any of the Services, or with redaction of your personal information, please email customer service at info@kriscarr.com for assistance. Please note that we may not be able to remove your information from the records of any third parties who have received your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

At our discretion, we may determine that your lack of engagement in the Services indicates your desire to opt-out of the Services. For example, you may be removed from our email list if you have not opened an email from us for a certain period of time. You may opt-in again at any time.

## HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?

We will retain your information indefinitely until you opt-out, request removal or redaction, or we choose to remove it. 

## PRIVACY OF CHILDREN

We are in compliance with the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. The Sites are not directed to children under the age of 13 and therefore we will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. 

We require users under 18 to obtain the consent of a parent or guardian to view the Sites. You agree to abide by any such restrictions and not to help anyone avoid these restrictions. 

## SECURITY POLICY

By using the Sites, you assume the risk of an unauthorized security breach. Even though we take prudent and reasonable measures to secure your personal information, our servers and our physical premises, we cannot guarantee that our efforts will be completely effective. 

## CONSENT TO TRANSFER

The Sites are operated from the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our Sites, participating in any of the Services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.

## CHANGES IN SITE OWNERSHIP

In the event of a merger, acquisition, or sale of any of our assets or the Sites, you consent to the disclosure to, and use by, any subsequent owner or operator of the Sites, of any information about you contained in our databases.
